A twice burnt match.
For this you need a match, you need a knife and you need a marker.
This is a really old staple of restaurant magic, usually it's done with paper matches.
I took it a kind of step further and carved up a wooden match so it resembles a burnt match, because as the match burns it eats away at the wood.
So we want to emulate that by carving the corners of the matchstick away, so starting at the head of the match just carve downwards about a quarter away down the matchstick until you have a kind of a shape that looks like a burnt match.
Then take the marker and color the head of the matchstick and most of what you carved.
See because it's now rough and uneven the color isn't going straight down, it's kind of just grabbing corners and edges of the stick.
When you're done with that, you take your pretend burnt match, put it in the crutch of your thumb like this.
Hold another match, strike the first match, make sure you get at least a quarter of it burnt, blow it out.
Now, it looks like you're just going to, cool it down, but in reality you're just going to throw it down between your legs onto the floor.